thenextscoop.com 2019-04-13

# Privacy Policy - The Next Scoop

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which **Thenextscoop** (“we” or “us” or “our”) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://thenextscoop.com/ website (“Site”).

Please read this privacy policy carefully. If you do not agree with the terms of this privacy policy, please do not access the site. You are encouraged to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of updates.

We are committed to transparency and being compliant with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

This policy was last updated on May 24, 2018

## Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can deny supplying personally identification information, except that it may counter them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

## Automatically Collected information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Information automatically collected may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider’s utilized and other similar information.

## Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. The web browser of User drops cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and also to track information about them. The user is free to make changes to their web browser to refuse cookies, or to make alerts when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

## How we use collected information

 **Thenextscoop** may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  *  _To run and operate our Site_  
we may need your information display content on the Site correctly.
  *  _To improve customer service_  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  *  _To personalize user experience_

  * To understand how our services and resources are operated by our users on our site we may use accumulated information

  *  _To improve our Site_  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  *  _To send periodic emails_  
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

## How we protect your information

We ensure that there are appropriate mechanisms to collect, store and process data and thus having relevant security measures. We secure your personal data including username, password, transaction information and data stored on our site from unauthorized disclosure, access, alteration.

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. For the above outlined purpose we may share collective demographic information which doesn’t include your personal data regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers.

## Third-Party Service Providers

We may share your information with third parties that perform services for us or on our behalf, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service, and marketing assistance.

## Third party websites

Kindly note that we may have third party links or advertising contents of our partners, sponsors, advertisers, suppliers on our site. We have no control or not liable for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site. We advise you to be aware when browsing and submitting data to this websites as they have their own terms and policies, thus we are not responsible for its protection and privacy.

## Advertising

Our advertising partners may set cookies on our site deliverable to users that allow the ad server to recognize your computer thus compiling non-personal information each time and then send you an online advertisement. This will help the ad networks to provide advertisements that are of most interest to you. Use of cookies by any advertiser is not covered under this privacy policy. To learn on opt-out of major ad networks you can visit <https://websitebuilders.com/tools/advertiser-opt-out/>.

## Google Adsense

Ads served by Google uses DART cookies that facilitate to deliver ads to users as per their site visits or other sites visited on the Internet. DART does not track and use your personal information. It only makes use of information automatically collected by the browser. By visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> you may opt out of the use of DART cookie.

## Policy for Children

We do not sell products or provide services to children under the age of 13. If you found any data on our site we have collected from children under age 13, please contact us using the contact information provided below. We take immediate measures to delete the information from our servers.

## Retention Purpose

We don’t keep personal data that is no longer necessary for the purpose of which it is collected. We have determined the period of retention of each data on the basis of statutory requirement. In case where it is inevitable to specify period of retention in advance, we have determined the period based on its need. In order to protect the decisive interests of another natural person, we may retain personal data to comply with a legal obligation where such retention is required.

## 1.     Your Rights

  *  **Right to be Informed and Access**

You have right to be Informed and consent to process your personal data, and access to your personal data, includes details of purposes of the processing, the categories of personal data concerned and recipients of personal data.

  *  **Right to Rectify**

You have the right to have any inaccurate personal data about you rectified and, taking into account the purposes of the processing, to have any incomplete personal data about you completed.

  *  **Right to Erasure**

We ensure that personal data is not kept longer than is necessary for the purposes for which personal data is processed. You have the right to the erasure of personal data if you withdraw consent to consent-based processing; you object to the processing under certain rules of applicable data protection law; the processing is for direct marketing purposes; and the personal data have been unlawfully processed

## 2.     Changes to this privacy policy

Thenextscoop has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We insist that users shall frequently check this page to stay updated and informed on our process of protecting personal data we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## 3.     Your acceptance of these terms

By using the service, you show your acknowledgement to this policy. Please do not use our Site if you do not adhere to this policy. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.
